BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 17) 6178/017
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 17)
1922- 1936
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United States Department of Labor
Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS)
6178/017
31.5 cubic feet
31.5 linear ft.
Records (documents), collective labor agreements.
5833675
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, August 24, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 21, 2016
Biographical / Historical
The US Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS) was established in 1884 to collect information about employment and labor in the United States. As mandated by the 1947 Taft-Hartley Act, the BLS was formally tasked with responsibility for soliciting, collecting, and analyzing collective bargaining agreements (CBAs) from public and private establishments, and making the agreements publicly available. In the early 1980s, this was function was limited to union contracts made with employers of 1000 or more employees.
In 2002, the National Archives and Records Administration authorized the BLS to donate inactive, non-confidential agreements which were 5 years or more past their expiration date to the Kheel Center where they would be preserved and made available to the public. The Office of Labor-Management Services took over responsibility for collecting and analyzing CBAs in 2011, and continues this donor relationship with the Kheel Center.
Scope and Contents
The US Department of Labor Historical Collective Bargaining Agreements Collection, 6178, is made up of 21 series of expired public- and private-sector collective bargaining agreements dating from 1887 to 2003 and totals 685 linear feet plus 10 CDs of digitized documents and 320 reels of microfilm. In addition to the CBAs, a small volume of related documents such as union constitutions, pension and health plans submitted to the BLS, are also available.
Selected collective bargaining agreements from this collection were digitized with generous funding from the National Historic Publications and Records Commission (NHPRC), and the National Science Foundation (NSF). Because documents other than collective bargaining agreements were also collected and preserved here by the US Department of Labor, a folder containing material that has been digitized, may also contain material which has not been digitized such as constitutions, bylaws, working rules, life insurance plans, or other organizational documents. For access to non-digitized material, contact Kheel Center staff.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6178/001: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1) 6178/002: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 2) 6178/003: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 3) 6178/004: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 4) 6178/006: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 6) 6178/007: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 7) 6178/008: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 8) 6178/009: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 9) 6178/010: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 10) 6178/011: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 11) 6178/012: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 12) 6178/013: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 13) 6178/014: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 14) 6178/015: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 15) 6178/016: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 16) 6178/018: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 18) 6178/019: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 19) 6178/020: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 20) 6178/021(d): BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 21) Digital 6178/022 mf: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 22) on Microfilm 6178/023: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 23)
Industrial relations -- United States; Collective bargaining -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Brewing industry -- United States.; Collective labor agreements -- Stone industry and trade -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Construction industry -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Stone industry and trade -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Iron industry -- United States; Collective labor agreements --Printing industry -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Metal industry -- United States; Collective labor agreements -- Railroads -- United States; United States. Department of Labor -- Archives; United States. Bureau of Labor Statistics -- Archives
5833675
- Bank Clerks - Cleveland, OH, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Salesmen of Bakery Goods - Seattle, WA, 1914-1921 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  1914, 1916, 1918, 1919, 1920, 1921
- Bread Salesmen, Counters and Special Deliverymen - St. Louis, MO, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Women Binding Workers - Philadelphia, PA, 1915-1917 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  1915, 1917
- Bindery Women - Portland, OR, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  1916, 1917
- Bindery Women - Columbus, OH, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Bindery Women - Cleveland, OH, 1919-1924 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  1919-1921, 1924
- Bindery Women - Chicago, IL, 1916-1927 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Bindery Women - Boston, MA, 1913-1917 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Bindery Women - Baltimore, Mary., 1902-1918 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  1902, 1918
- Bindery Women - Denver, CO, 1911 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Bindery Women - San Francisco, CA, 1910-1913 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  1910, 1913
- Bindery Women - St. Louis, MO, 1918-1926 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  1918, 1920, 1926
- Bindery Women - Lansing, MI, 1898 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Bindery Women - New York, NY, 1906-1925 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  1906, 1918, 1919, 1920, 1924, 1925
- Bindery Women - Washington D.C., 1918 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Printer Bookbinders - Philadelphia, PA, 1913-1916 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  1913, 1916
- Blank Book Forwarders, Finishers, and Paper Cutters - Chicago, IL, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Bookbinders - Birmingham, AL, 1920-1926 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Bookbinders - Little Rock, AR, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Bookbinders - San Francisco, CA, 1910-1916 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  1910, 1916
- Bookbinders and Bindery Women - San Francisco, CA, 1919-1923 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Bookbinders - Colorado Springs, CO, 1903-1923 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  1903, 1923
- Bookbinders - Denver, CO, 1907-1917 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  1907, 1917
- Bookbinders - Washington D.C., 1900-1926 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  1900, 1920, 1921, 1926
- Bookbinders - South Bend, IN (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Bookbinders - Cedar Rapids, IA, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Bookbinders and Bindery Women - Des Moines, IA, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Bookbinders - Dubuque, IA, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Bookbinders - Frankfort, KY, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Bookbinders - New Orleans, LA, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Bookbinders - Baltimore, IN, 1909-1915 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  1909, 1915
- Bookbinders and Bindery Women - Baltimore, IN, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Bookbinders - Boston, MA, 1910-1913 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Book Cover Stampers - Boston, MA (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Bookbinders and Bindery Women - Boston, MA, 1920-1922 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  1920, 1922
- Bookbinders - Houston, TX, 1916-1922 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  1916, 1919-1922
- Bookbinders - Ft. Worth, TX, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Bookbinders and Bindery Women - Quincy, IL, 1918 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Bookbinders - Springfield, IL, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Bookbinders - Ft. Wayne, IN, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Bookbinders - Cambridge, MA, 1914-1918 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  1914, 1918
- Bindery Women - Cambridge, MA, 1913-1917 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  1913, 1917
- Bindery Women - Norwood, MA, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Bookbinders - Detroit, MI, 1916-1919 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  1916, 1919
- Bookbinders - Duluth, MN, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Bindery Women - Minneapolis, MN, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Bookbinders - St. Paul, MN, 1901 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Bookbinders - Kansas City, MO, 1911-1927 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  1911, 1916, 1918-1920, 1923, 1924, 1927
- Bookbinders - Bloomington, IL, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Finishers and Gilders - St. Louis, MO, 1916-1920 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  1916, 1920
- Blank Book Workers - New York, NY, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Bookbinders - Atlanta, GA, 1911 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Book Cover Stampers and Gold Leaf Layers - New York, NY, 1912-1918 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  1912, 1918
- Bookbinders and Paper Cutters - Chicago, IL, 1919-1922 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Printed Bookbinders and Papercutters - Chicago, IL, 1911-1923 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  1911, 1922, 1923
- Bookbinders - Los Angeles, CA, 1915-1921 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  1915, 1917, 1919, 1921
- Bookbinders and Paper Cutters - Chicago, IL, 1911-1923 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  1911, 1913, 1916, 1919-1921, 1923
- Bookbinders - St. Louis, MO, 1910-1920 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  1910, 1916, 1920
- Bookbinders and Blank Book Workers - Philadelphia, PA, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Bookbinders - Columbus, OH, 1915-1924 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  1915, 1917, 1921, 1924
- Bookbinders and Binding Women - Salt Lake City, UT, 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  1918, 1921
- Bookbinders - Richmond, VA, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Bookbinders - Seattle, WA, 1912-1919 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  1912, 1917-1919
- Bookbinders - Spokane, WA, 1911-1918 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  1911, 1918
- Bookbinders - Elm Grove, WV, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Bookbinders - Milwaukee, WI, 1916-1919 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  1916, 1917, 1919
- Bookbinders - St. Louis, MO, 1905-1916 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  1905, 1916
- Bookbinders - Lincoln, NE, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Bookbinders - Newark, NJ, 1908-1919 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  1908, 1913, 1916, 1919
- Bookbinders - Montana, 1911-1922 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  1911, 1921, 1922
- Bookbinders - New York, NY, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Printed Bookbinders - New York, NY, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Printed Bookbinders, Book Stampers, Gold Layers, Book Edge Guilders - New York, NY, 1915-1917 (Box 1, Folder 74)
- Bookbinders - New York, NY, 1918 (Box 1, Folder 75)
- Printed Bookbinders - New York, NY, 1918-1921 (Box 1, Folder 76)
- Bookbinders - Albany, NY, 1921-1922 (Box 1, Folder 77)
- Bookbinders - Newark, NJ, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 78)
- Bookbinders, Book Edge Gilders, and Marblers - New York, NY, 1905-1911 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  1905, 1911
- Bookbinders - Indianapolis, IN, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 80)
- Bookbinders and Bindery Women - Indianapolis, IN, 1910-1924 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  1910, 1912, 1915-1918, 1921-1924
- Bookbinders - Philadelphia, PA, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 82)
- Bookbinders - LaFayette, IN, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 83)
- Bookbinders - Pittsburgh, PA, 1902-1919 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  1902, 1917, 1919
- Bookbinders - Scranton, PA, 1917-1919 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  1917, 1919
- Bookbinders - Williamsport, PA, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 86)
- Bookbinders - Providence, RI, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 87)
- Bookbinders - Nashville, TN, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 88)
- Bookbinders - Dallas, TX, 1915-1919 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  1915, 1919
- Bookbinders - Akron, OH (Box 1, Folder 90)
- Bookbinders - Cincinnati, OH, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 91)
- Bookbinders - Fargo, ND, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 92)
- Bookbinders - Raleigh, NC, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 93)
- Bookbinders - Toledo, OH, 1904-1920 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  1904, 1920
- Bookbinders and Bindery Women - Youngstown, OH, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 95)
- Bookbinders - Portland, OR, 1911 (Box 1, Folder 96)
- Bookbinders and Bindery Women - Portland, OR, 1918 (Box 1, Folder 97)
- Bookbinders - Harrisburg, PA, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 98)
- Printed Bookbinders - Philadelphia, PA, 1912-1915 (Box 1, Folder 99)
- Bookbinders - Boston, MA, 1918-1919 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  1918, 1919
- Bookkeepers, Stenographers, and Accountants Union - New York, NY, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 101)
- Bootblacks - Chicago, IL, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 102)
- Bricklayers - Rock Island, IL, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 103)
- Bricklayers - Pittsburgh, PA, 1912 (Box 1, Folder 104)
- Soda Drivers - Cincinnati, OH, 1916-1919 (Box 1, Folder 105)
- Beer Drivers - Los Angeles, CA, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 106)
- Brewery Stablemen - Chicago, IL, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 107)
- Beer Drivers - New York, NY, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 108)
- Brewery Drivers - Spokane, WA, 1902-1905 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  1902, 1905
- Beer Drivers - Memphis, TN, 1912 (Box 1, Folder 110)
- Brewery Drivers - Pittsburgh, PA, 1915-1917 (Box 1, Folder 111)
- Beer Drivers and Stablemen - Cincinnati, OH, 1915-1916 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  1915, 1916
- Beer Drivers and Stablemen - Buffalo, NY, 1916-1919 (Box 1, Folder 113)
- Bottlers and Drivers - New York, NY, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 114)
- Beer Wagon Drivers and Helpers - Chicago, IL, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 115)
- Bottle Beer and Liquor Wagon Drivers and Chauffeurs - Chicago, IL, 1914-1922 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  1914, 1917, 1922
- Drivers and Stablemen - Baltimore, Mary., 1915-1917 (Box 1, Folder 117)
- Bottlers and Drivers - Springfield, MA, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 118)
- Beer Bottlers, Wagon Drivers, and Chauffeurs - Cleveland, OH, 1917-1919 (Box 1, Folder 119)
- Beer Drivers and Chauffeurs - Cleveland, OH, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 120)
- Beer Drivers, Stablemen, and Helpers - Minneapolis, MN, 1916-1917 (Box 1, Folder 121)
- Drivers and Stablemen (soda and mineral water) - Indianapolis, IN, 1916-1919 (Box 1, Folder 122)
- Beer Drivers and Stablemen - Indianapolis, IN, 1916-1919 (Box 1, Folder 123)
- Drivers and Stablemen - Newark, NJ, 1909-1915 (Box 1, Folder 124)
- Bottlers and Teamsters - Omaha, NE, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 125)
- Drivers and Stablemen - Salt Lake City, UT, 1913-1915 (Box 1, Folder 126)
  1913, 1915
- Bottlers and Bottle Beer Drivers - Cincinnati, OH, 1914-1918 (Box 1, Folder 127)
  1914, 1916, 1918
- Salesmen of Bakery Goods - Tacoma, WA, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 128)
- Bottlers and Drivers - Providence, RI, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 129)
- Beer Drivers and Stablemen - Washington D.C., 1910-1916 (Box 1, Folder 130)
  1910, 1914, 1916
- Bottlers and Drivers - Portland, OR, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 131)
- Beer Drivers and Stablemen - Youngstown, OH, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 132)
- Brewery Workers, Teamsters and Chauffeurs - Scranton, PA, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 133)
- Beer Drivers, Bottle Beer Drivers, Stablemen, Yardmen, and Firemen - Denver, CO, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 134)
- Bottle Beer Drivers and Stablemen - San Francisco, CA, 1913-1917 (Box 1, Folder 135)
  1913, 1915, 1917
- Keg Beer Drivers and Stablemen - San Francisco, CA, 1915-1924 (Box 1, Folder 136)
  1915, 1917, 1924
- Drivers and Stablemen - St. Paul, MN, 1914-1915 (Box 1, Folder 137)
  1914, 1915
- Beer Drivers and Stablemen - Detroit, MI, 1914-1920 (Box 1, Folder 138)
- Beer Drivers and Stablemen - St. Louis, MO, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 139)
- Beer Drivers and Stablemen - Lexington, KY, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 140)
- Beer Drivers, Stablemen, and Bottlers - Louisville, KY, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 141)
- Drivers and Stablemen - New Orleans, LA, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 142)
- Beer Drivers and Stablemen - Kansas City, MO, 1915-1918 (Box 1, Folder 143)
- Soda Drivers - Kansas City, MO, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 144)
- Beer Drivers and Stablemen - St. Louis, MO, 1914-1919 (Box 1, Folder 145)
- Car Makers - Philadelphia, PA, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 146)
- Car Workers - Jersey Shore, PA (Box 1, Folder 147)
- Carpenters - Seattle, WA, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 148)
- Carpenters - Hudson County, NJ, 1906-1917 (Box 1, Folder 149)
  1906-1907, 1917
- Carpenters - Dobbs Ferry, NY, 1902 (Box 1, Folder 150)
- Carpenters - Schenectady, NY, 1913-1925 (Box 1, Folder 151)
  1913-1915, 1923-1925
- Carpenters - Fort Lee, NJ, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 152)
- Carpenters - Hackensack, NJ, 1905-1907 (Box 1, Folder 153)
- Carpenters - Seattle, WA, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 154)
- Carpenters - Tamaqua, PA, 1915-1924 (Box 1, Folder 155)
  1915, 1924
- Carpenters - Wyoming Valley, PA, 1903-1925 (Box 1, Folder 156)
  1903, 1923-1925
- Carpenters - York, PA, 1907-1924 (Box 1, Folder 157)
  1907, 1923, 1924
- Carpenters - Scranton, PA, 1913-1928 (Box 1, Folder 158)
- Carpenters - Reading, PA, 1903-1924 (Box 1, Folder 159)
  1903-1905, 1922-1924
- Carpenters - Pittsburgh, PA, 1914-1924 (Box 1, Folder 160)
- Carpenters - Clarks Summit, PA, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 161)
- Carpenters - Conshohocken, PA, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 162)
- Carpenters - Erie, PA, 1915-1925 (Box 1, Folder 163)
  1915, 1923-1925
- Carpenters - Freeland, PA, 1906-1907 (Box 1, Folder 164)
- Carpenters - Grove City, PA, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 165)
- Carpenters - Harrisburg, PA, 1923-1925 (Box 1, Folder 166)
  1923, 1925
- Carpenters - Hazelton, PA, 1903-1906 (Box 1, Folder 167)
  1903, 1906
- Carpenters - Jeannette, PA (Box 1, Folder 168)
- Carpenters - Johnstown, PA, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 169)
- Carpenters - Kane, PA, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 170)
- Carpenters - Kittanning, PA, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 171)
- Carpenters - Lehigh Valley, PA, 1919-1924 (Box 1, Folder 172)
  1919, 1923, 1924
- Carpenters - Mahanoy City, PA, 1902 (Box 1, Folder 173)
- Carpenters - McAdoo, PA, 1905-1907 (Box 1, Folder 174)
- Carpenters - New Castle, PA, 1904-1925 (Box 1, Folder 175)
  1904, 1923-1925
- Carpenters - Peckville, PA, 1906-1926 (Box 1, Folder 176)
  1906, 1925-1926
- Carpenters - Philadelphia, PA, 1910-1927 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Carpenters - Houston, TX, 1913-1924 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  1913, 1916-1920, 1923-1924
- Carpenters - Jacksonville, MS, 1902 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Carpenters - Paterson, NJ, 1902-1906 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Carpenters - Ridgewood, NJ, 1904-1906 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Carpenters - Trenton, NJ, 1923-1927 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Carpenters - Milwaukee, WI, 1915-1928 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  1915-1918, 1926-1928
- Millmen - Essex County, NJ, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Carpenters - Syracuse, NY, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Carpenters - New York, NY, 1905-1916 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  1905, 1909, 1916
- Carpenters - New Rochelle, NY, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Carpenters - Cleveland, OH, 1916-1920 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Carpenters - Columbus, OH, 1916-1923 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  1916, 1920, 1923
- Carpenters - Dayton, OH, 1925-1927 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Carpenters - Falconer, NY, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Carpenters - Geneva, NY, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Carpenters - East Liverpool, OH, 1918-1923 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  1918, 1923
- Carpenters - Findlay, OH, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Carpenters - Marietta, OH, 1905 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Carpenters - Marion, OH, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Carpenters - New Philadelphia, OH, 1903 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Carpenters - Janesville, WI, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Carpenters - Green Bay, WI, 1905 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Carpenters - Weirton, WV, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Carpenters - Wheeling, WV, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Carpenters - Sistersville, WV, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Carpenters - Morgantown, WV, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Carpenters - Huntington, WV, 1903 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Carpenters - Elkins, WV, 1903 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Carpenters - Kenosha, WI, 1920-1923 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  1920, 1923
- Carpenters - Brookville, PA, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Carpenters - Carbondale, PA, 1904-1921 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  1904, 1921
- Carpenters - Pennsylvania (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Carpenters - Charleroi, PA, 1905 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Carpenters - Jackson, TN, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Carpenters - Memphis, TN, 1914-1924 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  1914, 1917, 1924
- Carpenters - Knoxville, TN, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Carpenters - Pittsburgh, PA, 1914-1923 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  1914, 1923
- Carpenters - Reading, PA, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Carpenters - Rhode Island, 1914-1923 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Carpenters - Pawtucket, RI, 1903-1906 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Carpenters - Westerly, RI, 1929 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Carpenters - Charleston, SC, 1923-1926 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Carpenters - Woonsocket, RI, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Carpenters - Chattanooga, TN, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Carpenters - Pittsburgh, PA, 1906-1924 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  1906, 1916-1917, 1921-1924
- Carpenters - Orange, TX, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Carpenters - Houston, TX, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Carpenters - Port Arthur, TX, 1916-1924 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  1916, 1924
- Carpenters - San Antonio, TX, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Carpenters - Sherman, TX, 1905 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Carpenters - Taylor, TX, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Carpenters - Weatherford, TX, 1901 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Carpenters - Utah, 1905-1925 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  1905-1907, 1916-1920, 1925
- Carpenters - Salt Lake City, UT, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Carpenters - St. Johnsbury, VT (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Carpenters - Clifton Forge, VA (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Carpenters - Norfolk, VA, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Carpenters - Richmond, VA, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Carpenters - Petersburg, VA, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Carpenters - Puget Sound, 1916 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Carpenters - Everett, WA, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Carpenters - Georgetown, WA (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Carpenters - Seattle, WA, 1913-1925 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  1913, 1917, 1919, 1925
- Carpenters - Hoquiam, WA, 1905 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Carpenters - Warren, OH, 1902-1905 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Carpenters - Xenia, OH, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Carpenters - Youngstown, OH, 1917-1924 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  1917, 1923-1924
- Carpenters - Omaha, NE, 1923-1924 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Carpenters - Pomeroy, OH, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Carpenters - Portsmouth, OH, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Carpenters - Rayland, OH (Box 2, Folder 72)
- Carpenters - Toledo, OH, 1920-1923 (Box 2, Folder 73)
- Carpenters - Sheboygan, WI, 1914-1925 (Box 2, Folder 74)
- Carpenters - Sheridan, WY, 1904 (Box 2, Folder 75)
- Carpenters - n/a, 1903-1906 (Box 2, Folder 76)
- Carpenters - St. Catherines, Ontario, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 77)
- Carpenters - Winnipeg, Canada, 1903 (Box 2, Folder 78)
- Catholic and Natural Union of Carpenters - Montreal, Canada, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 79)
- Carpenters - LaCrosse, WI, 1925 (Box 2, Folder 80)
- Carpenters - Nashville, TN, 1917-1920 (Box 2, Folder 81)
- Carpenters - Brownwood, TX, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 82)
- Carpenters - Dallas, TX, 1912-1913 (Box 2, Folder 83)
- Carpenters - Red Bank, NJ (Box 2, Folder 84)
- Carpenters - New Jersey, 1906-1919 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  1906, 1910, 1917-1919
- Carpenters - Newark, NJ, 1914 (Box 2, Folder 86)
- Carpenters - Passaic and Rutherford, NJ, 1919-1920 (Box 2, Folder 87)
- Carpenters - Paterson, NJ, 1903 (Box 2, Folder 88)
- Carpenters - Omaha, NE, 1921 (Box 2, Folder 89)
- Carpenters - Portsmouth, NH, 1902 (Box 2, Folder 90)
- Carpenters - New Jersey, 1904 (Box 2, Folder 91)
- Carpenters - Atlantic City, NJ, 1910-1920 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  1910, 1920
- Carpenters - Atlantic Highlands, NJ, 1905-1906 (Box 2, Folder 93)
- Carpenters - Bergen County, NJ, 1905-1921 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  1905, 1921
- Carpenters - Camden, NJ, 1905 (Box 2, Folder 95)
- Carpenters - Essex County, NJ, 1920-1924 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  1920, 1924
- Carpenters - Glen Cove, NY, 1924 (Box 2, Folder 97)
- Carpenters - Ithaca, NY, 1923-1925 (Box 2, Folder 98)
- Carpenters - Jamestown, NY, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 99)
- Carpenters - Kingston, NY, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 100)
- Carpenters - Lindenhurst, NY, 1902 (Box 2, Folder 101)
- Carpenters - Rochester, NY, 1916-1926 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  1916-1920, 1923-1926
- Stairbuilders - Cincinnati, OH, 1911-1913 (Box 2, Folder 103)
- Parquet Floor Layers - Cleveland, OH, 1913-1923 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  1913-1914, 1917-1918, 1923
- Carpenters - Dallas, TX, 1915-1923 (Box 2, Folder 105)